Why don't you go?
Did you go into the seawater earlier?
My dad bought it for me
Is it broken?
I stopped for a moment
Director!
Sorry, sorry, director!
It was good, really
Why? What's wrong with you?
Wolbaek can’t come.
- What?
- He said he had chicken pox.
Hey, then what about filming tomorrow?
What about filming the day after tomorrow?
ah! Hey, what should I do!
Hey, it's too far from here, I can't come back
There, boy!
Do you live in this neighborhood?
Have your parents gone to work?
Mom went to work at the factory
My dad is a poet
Mom...
Because you don’t come home often
I don't know where it is
- Why?
- Oh, look at this guy.
Is your answer too harsh?
Could you please tell me your parents' contact information?
We're filming a movie
I'm going to audition right on the spot.
That opportunity came to me
Was it luck or misfortune?
Hey, hey, hey, where
Did you bring a kid like that?
Well done, great job.
Why are you so good at this?
Are you good at it?
- Really?
- Yes
I'll come back when the sun rises brightly
Must!
mom!
Mom is here!
our beautiful son
Oh my!
Let's go to Seoul
Now all that's left is to succeed
Mom
I'm going to be a manager now.
Then we will always be together
Huh? Then go to Seoul
Can you stay with your mom all the time?
Of course
Oh, my mom
To give it to you, voila!
Wow, those are shoes?
open it
An unknown opportunity
I held on desperately
I wonder if it's a string that connects the family.
Try them on
Best Actor Award
Seon Woo-hae from the movie ‘Ewha, Wolbaek’!
She is 11 years old, she is the youngest!
Hello
This is Seon Woo-hae, who played Wolbaek.
With all children
I want to share this honor with you
Thank you
Grow up and grow up. Grow up and down.
No.
There must be purity
It grants wishes
Pure strength because of you
My parents lost it
I can't see it anywhere
It's so hard I'm dying
Do not leave any scars
You mean get off?
Why our sun?
You've grown a lot in the past year.
Who is with Taerin?
Would you like to see them as brother and sister?
- Wow, director.
- mother
just one more time
Please think about it, okay?
- Director
- Me, mother
If there's anything good next time
I'll contact you
Oh, where's next, coach?
mom!
Mom, now we
Are you going to buy new sneakers?
I need to control my diet starting today.
the bigger you are
You need to get smaller, you know?
I couldn't find a reason to quit
I couldn't quit
Ah, director, hello.
that movie
You know ‘Harry Potter’, right?
This is the Korean version
I'm going to make it myself
Really?
I'm giving you a special chance first.
You have to catch it
What can I do?
Ah, thanks to the director, our year has improved
I suddenly became a star
Most frauds start with faith.
How to go out
Would you like to have a meal?
belief that this will happen
belief that it will be real
If you didn't believe it
Director, this swindler
It was a debt that would not accumulate.
Just get caught, really.
If you didn't believe it in the first place
It's okay if you doubted it
I feel stupid
This...
I'm sorry
Um, I guess mom is crazy
Our year...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry mom
Dad is that kid
They're going out to catch you
You'll get it soon, right?
That's okay, okay?
That's fine then
sorry for me
Because I'm small
No, when I grow up
How much your mom loves you!
Do you trust mom and dad? uh?
You have to believe it
Yes, I believe it.
I think I learned it too early
comes from disbelief
There is also comfort
You have to believe it!
It's sparkling
Not everything is a gem
A victim of entertainment fraud
Actor Seon Woo-hae's mother
At home this afternoon
was found dead
The first to discover the current site
Seon Woo-hae
I am guarding the ceremony hall alone.
I was then
I think that's what I thought.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Get out of the way, get out of the way
- Are you in debt?
- Hey, take a quick picture!
Is it all over when I die? Does it end when you die? uh?
- Where's your dad?
- Are there any adults?
- Speak, speak!
- Where did you go?
- Hey, that's enough, that's enough, that's enough
- You don't know where your father is.
You signed this...
What is this?
- Ha, indeed!
- Hey.
- Are you his dad?
- No, no.
My father, my father, my father!
- What are you going to do with my money?
- Stop making movies.
- Father, nobleman, here, here
- Hey.
Sign here...
Hey, where are you going?
What are you going to do with my money?
What kind of acting should you do in times like this?
I don't know if I should do it
maybe
I hope someone shouts cut sign
Maybe I was waiting
Cut, okay
Mom, let's go home!
Filming will end someday
Because that's the end of that acting.
What kind of god is this?
I like that person
It's being replaced
- Happy Birthday
- Dear Seonwoohae
My acting was good
It wasn't bad
Why do I dream...
Due to untimely bad weather
Ship departure is canceled
They say it has become more frequent.
For those planning a domestic trip:
Not the sea
How about going to the mountains?
The sea with refreshing waves crashing
A mountain full of greenery
We shared our schedule with you.
Because of Taerin’s documentary
There is local shooting
They said they filmed it as soon as they came up to Seoul.
It's also an emotional scene
Oh, do you make your schedule like this?
Ha...
Jeyeonah
Call the representative
Was it better?
I hope it becomes a hot topic like this
People will watch the show more
Representative, I’m not
I'm talking about that video that was uploaded.
I kept trying to contact you.
Not even the seeds were eaten...
Isn’t the world supposed to be like this?
Such sensitive and private parts...
I got off
After going through a really cumbersome process
thank you
Thank you so much
Ah, thank goodness
Reporters will never let you down.
The article that originally came out was
There was no problem
in a follow up article
The bastard with the video attached is the problem.
keep an eye on
Try to be friendly
Is there anything more that will explode?
Seonwoohae
Even when I was at our school
Because of the hardships of living
There were a lot of rumors
It wasn't all real
just your life
I feel like I lived faithfully...
Did you fall in love with it, not Taerin?
Even the parts that the CEO hates
I feel like you care.
The production team
You must have received an appearance contract, right?
I changed my mind about that thing
If you say you won't do it
A lot of people are in trouble, check it yourself
yes
You didn't receive it?
Ha...
No, Amman suddenly
Even if you come in
There's something else to forget
Hey, can you take it for me?
I'll put it in my email now
I don't like it
I absolutely hate it, I absolutely hate it
Heart?
Was he this kind of kid?
Where has the florist gone?
Oh, I came too
The door is locked
I guess he's away
You're delivering happiness
Ah, this is so...
But who are you?
Who is that? For what reason...
I love kimchi...
I am a colleague...
No, friend, no, classmate.
Oh, really?
Ah, there
I'm dad
Oh my, wow
- Oh, hello.
- Yes, hello.
hello
I am that...
Oh my, I lost my wallet...
I'm filming with Hae right now.
Ah, this is my sister’s company...
근데 저기, 우리 해 괜찮나요?
I heard something bad appeared
I guess you came because you were worried.
Yeah, well, I deserve it.
I don't know if it exists
Uh, son!
Are you coming to deliver happiness?
Are you here?
Why did you come?
huh?
Oh my! Dad made kimchi
Kimchi is also essential at home.
I have kimchi at home
Go, it's closing time soon.
Hey, the sun is high in the sky
What do you mean by finishing...
It's okay because I saw your face, yeah
- Come in.
- Oh no, no.
Oh, just give me this instead...
Uh, hey, son, don't come out! Dad go
Have fun with friends...
See you again
- Come in.
- Yes, yes
Where did you go?
That...
Should withered flowers be collected separately?
Withered flowers are general trash
Ah...
The blue thing you gave me before
Because it withered
Hey, do you still have it plugged in?
Throw it away, it's rude to the flowers too, that's rude.
Why are you smiling?
huh? I feel better
Seong Je-yeon
Have you ever
- Am I awkward?
- No, that can't be possible. Why me?
Oh, no.
Then '1, uncomfortable'
'2, pitiful'
What are you saying...
neither
Did I ask you to hug me for no reason?
About that video
- What comes with the article
- Yes
The representative gave it to me
Because I said thank you for you
you
You don't have to worry
What was I thankful for?
Reporters usually don't take it down.
Thank you for your hard work
um
The timing is really weird though
Huh?
appearance contract
No, that's why I brought it with me today...
Are you here for this?
seal
Are you going to take a picture?
From now on, just
Let’s talk about business first
Don't try to find a topic
No, that's not it, no...
That's true, but...
Oh, really
Everyone says I'm easy, very
- Just one mic...
- Oh, yes.
Have you been noisy these past few days?
You refused to appear because you were afraid of this.
You must have grown up...
Actually, I hadn't even thought about it that far.
I didn't even know there was all that left.
I'm sorry
If you have decided to give up now,
I'll do really well
No
On the air because of me
It's okay if you don't bother anyone.
till the end
Please take care of me
thank you
- Thank you
- thank you
- Uh, Nuri.
- Oppa
Don't you think it needs an explanation?
What do you think you are filming?
Where are you?
Let me explain
Are you really crazy about money?
Nowadays, going on broadcasts is also
I heard they all pay
There's no way my brother would do something that costs money.
There is no
An ordinary flower shop that broadcasters say is crazy
I'm not even going to advertise it
Um, no
- What is it?
- So
What is your question?
I just wanted to criticize
I think I'm crazy about money
Excuse me
Ah, yes
The ice cream you ordered arrived.
- Thank you
- me and
I won't take any money
They always hand out flowers.
Ah...
Thank you, I will enjoy it.
thank you
Oh, just...
What I looked like when I was young
We'll go out together
You have to be young to show off your youthful appearance.
But brother, if there are still flowers left,
Did you just spray it nearby?
Then we're in big trouble, really, huh?
Eat it, it will melt.
eat a lot
- Mmm!
- delicious?
uh?
Ah, when PD is looking for coffee
I think it's done
Ah
Who?
hello
It's my younger brother
Are you filming with your brother?
It really grew a lot
hello, me
I am the manager of an actor I am filming with.
But how do you know me?
My brother and I are already like that
Have you become friends?
Ah...
You don't remember.
When I was young
I also read a book to you.
A book?
Book...
‘A small stone
'I just fell in'
My brother likes her too
Sister, good luck with your filming!
Share it together
What he ate...
It was nice to meet you!
You've really grown up a lot
I guess I didn't see my younger brother.
Thank goodness
Ah...
Let's grow up
- Is this your brother?
- Yes
What, why not?
Why did it become like this?
No, what happened to me? Everyone...
Oh, really
To me, you always grew up.
He's so small
But it's so pretty, girl
Aren’t you pretty now?
When are you going to bring your report card?
pretty
The prettiest in the world
- The world is beautiful
- It's late, you.
Isn't it too late yet?
Hey
That sister from earlier
You're that sister, right?
you come to work
- You come to work.
- That's right.
What are your grades like?
You keep hiding it, huh?
Hey, Eunuri, talk to your brother.
Uh, the weather is nice so I’m sad to go home.
Senior Jeyeon, why aren’t you answering the phone?
How do I know that?
Steady hobby life
It seems like they do it
To people at work
They never told me
You didn’t even go hiking with me today.
So
After it's over, there's nothing to do
Why are you telling me that?
Huh? Are you free?
Uh, I have a day off today.
Can I go play?
Oh, you're bored too.
The filming team was busy working hard.
It's quiet, but don't you feel lonely?
I'll see you in a few days.
Should I see it again today?
Are you going to drink coffee? I'll buy it, uh
Telling me not to come
I'm continuing, huh?
Hello
W...
I hung up
Oh my, hello
hello
It's our first time here, so
Can I ask you the directions?
Sorry, I got lost too...
Oh, you see!
But your energy is so good
Ah, thank you
Do you work in the art world?
My ancestors are grateful
I think you've accumulated a lot.
Do you know our ancestors?
I told you not to go alone
Baby
Ouch!
You had company.
I think you don't know
How can we help you?
Would you like me to join you?
I usually talk to you when I'm alone.
thank you for your help
I'm very shy
I'm all nervous watching it
I tried helping
Are you nervous?
I'm afraid I'll cry again
emotional threshold
I think it's a bit low.
What was the threshold?
needed to cause a reaction
minimal stimulation intensity
Flippers?
Oh, I'm free diving.
Ah...
I can hold my breath well.
The end?
too short
Yes?
The banner over there is long.
I would like you to read it
I'm shy, but I have to say what I have to say.
It must be hard to live
Ah, why are you worrying about me...
Could you please tell me right now?
Are you working?
You almost took the real work earlier.
I'm doing this now
What is the work?
I was just speaking informally earlier.
You said 'baby'
I'm trying to pretend that we're in the same group.
Ah...
‘Baby’ was a bit like that.
Where is your destination?
I wish it was close
If you leave it on the street
I wonder where the work will take again.
Yes, this is my destination
From now on, you can see it on your phone
There are a lot of apps for maps, taxis, etc.
You're with that friend
Have a nice visit
Stop looking, your face will pierce.
Are you always this kind?
Be careful of people like this
Don't just follow along
Get out of the way, don't block the entrance
Oppa, get out of the way, don’t block the entrance.
What kind of power does he have...
Do you take any medicine?
What are you?
That's right
The destination was the same
Oh no
What is he?
'Self'
‘Baby’
Why do you find yourself here?
Why did it have to be ‘self’?
There must have been ‘Friend’ too.
Make a hobby
Don't do this here, please
I came here for a hobby
Do you want to join us too? free diving
What do you do?
But if it's 'friend'
Should we even drink alcohol together?
Like my oppa and Jeyeon senior
That's right, I remembered
Even when you were young, you really talked about other people
You weren't listening, right?
no
What about alcohol, it’s a waste of money
Alcohol?
I'll buy it, eat it with me too
I hate it
I knocked it over earlier
thank you
Then to Seong Je-yeon
I guess I should try asking him out for a drink.
-Customer is calling now...
- Huh? He refuses
My senior told me there was a fire.
I texted you, will you come?
Huh?
Ah, I told my senior
There's something I couldn't talk about
I didn't ask
Why? I'm curious
Hello
Oh, what is it?
I am holding your actor hostage.
If you want to take me, come here
Mo Taerin, I heard there was a fire! where are you? Did you turn it off?
Is anyone hurt?
What are you?
I found it
You were there too
Shouldn’t there be?
This is my flower shop
Oh, that's right
What happens if the flower shop catches fire?
flame
Flame!
I'm careful not to hit women.
You hit me today, uh, motaerin
You were surprised
Where can I hit you?
Oh, really
Or even you.
-Where should I hit?
- That's right, you're not worth hitting.
- Brother
- Uh, why, why?
This is the genealogy I made
- Ah...
- Tell Nuri to prepare for the lesson.
- Testing this week
- Yes
What are you?
tutor
Who are you teaching?
my brother
Oh, really?
What do you believe in him...
Hey, Seong Je-yeon
Why don't you say anything to your brother?
When did I?
Hey, but
If everyone is done with their business
Would it be okay for everyone to go?
Why are you two brothers?
Is it real?
- Yes
- No
Huh?
We'll leave now
Yeah, let's go
- Go now?
- We'll go.
- I'm going
- Uh, go.
I'll go, see you tomorrow
Don't come for a while
Wasn't it?
It wasn't
Until when?
You never know
I wish I had bought the flower basket here
Maybe they were brothers
Hey, it's still that
I kept it in it
Cute, really
Are you in good condition?
I think there was a bad article
Because I failed when I was young
Do you have a unique mindset?
I feel like I'm falling apart
I know how it is
I can't make fun of you
Aren't you going?
I'm going, I'm going
The rest who are not brothers are leaving.
Make sure to prepare for study
Oh, it's quiet.
Right?
What is it?
Last time, during the function test, why
It was just the two of us who fell side by side.
I was nervous at that time
You were so loud.
Don't you remember me?
We fell together
Should I even remember it?
I got a dispatch card
Oh, that was last week?
Just what I want to remember
I remembered it
Ah
Like this, like this
It was fate that we met
We'll be together this time, yeah
don't betray
It’s been a while since I met someone in Korea.
I'm so excited
I have a great personality
You're bright
Yes, ah, then again...
- Yes
- Yes, next time too.
I saw it last week
We fell together
Ah, that license number.
If I fix this right away
Do you feel like someone who waited?
Words change so quickly
I think you guessed it.
The room director is very involved with the company.
You had influence.
I also raised a lot of juniors.
separate from other employees
Don't worry, we haven't talked about anything.
It should be a warm ending, right?
Cheering...
It doesn't work today
Will it work tomorrow?
Like the CEO
There was a time when I wanted to be
Pretty desperately.
women who work here
Isn’t that what you’re saying?
But
As the representative goes further and further,
It made me want to make a side road.
I want you
Because you’re not afraid of me
There were good times
I'm getting more and more
I got scared, the CEO
Thank you so much
Wow
Can I ask why you quit?
Am I the only one who is surprised?
How is Team Manager Seong’s company?
Do you think you might want to work?
Oh...
This is my first time hearing this question.
I think that’s a really good question.
What company do you want to work for?
It's a utopia, there
not the company
The answer is really not that good, right?
Ah...
I am
A company where you two are not together
I can't imagine
At some point
It was difficult to deal with the CEO.
Question marks keep popping up
The CEO’s rules and methods
Who am I going to blame now?
What are your goals at this company?
The representative’s beliefs
Is this really your belief?
Director, what is your goal?
me? Working only according to my own judgment
No, my judgment is correct.
Proving it
Don't cut back on sleep
Ha...
No, mom, that's delivery.
I told you I sent it home
Not the study room
I even bought a mask pack for my aunt.
Share it together
- Goodbye.
- Uh, go in.
Okay, stop nagging.
Ah, that old sitcom baby
Are you saying it's on TV?
Are you still pretty?
Wow, she was really pretty.
- How did he grow up?
- I don't know.
He grew up ugly, whatever.
Are you starting a company?
- Huh?
- huh?
Oh, no, no, talking to myself.
What?
Hey
I teach myself
I thought you had talent
I think I made a good decision not to go into education.
while I'm away
You take care of your meal
Where are you going?
To plant a tree
Well, I know the child's grades and the tree...
Are you Spinoza?
What's wrong, brother? huh?
Eunuri, tell me
You know Spinoza, don’t you?
I'll really check it out when I come back.
Report card, huh?
Brother, use my suitcase carefully
Even when I was on a school trip
It was really beautifully written, that!
Take my baby... buy me one?
Hey, do you really not know?
Or did you feed it to me?
Both?
Disposable camera? It's been a while
I've never done this before
Don't use it, it's amazing.
Oh, she was the Gangnam princess, right?
You must have used an expensive camera.
This body
There was a time when I was a princess
- I'll take a picture for you.
- Yes
one, two
- Oh, it's pretty.
- Yes
one more time
one, two
So pretty
Uh, okay, okay.
How should I give you motion sickness medicine?
water?
No, I think this will be resolved by sleeping.
Please look at the sea too.
Ah, the scenery is nice!
Oh my, that's good!
sea, sea
Hey, I like the wind!
You two, just pretend to be friendly with each other.
Shall we laugh?
- Are you pretending to be friends?
- I'm not close with this guy.
Pretending to be just a little friendly
- 'Ahaha'!
-Ahahahaha!
No, no, really no!
You can't do this
It really doesn't work
Oh no
Looks like kids, hey, looks like kids
You worked hard
Huh? trash
- Shall we do it together?
- Uh, let's do it together.
- Shall we take a picture of that?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, come quickly.
- Let's do this together!
Why is there so much trash?
Throw it away anywhere, oh
I've grown up a lot
'I heard it a lot'
'Look at him for a moment, do you see him?'
'In the water like this
Was there a scene that was filmed?'
- Are you asking me to say my lines like this?
- Yes
This is how you do it
Then my brother
'Don't you remember? Me that morning...
Ah, the scenery is really
So pretty
Writer, here's more.
- Wow, thank you.
- Yes
No, that senior
He just takes pictures
I planned something like this...
Taerin, is it difficult?
Kid...
What should I do?
No, it's not hard.
You did a great job practicing shoveling, right?
Yeah, if you like it...
You can drive a truck here
Is there anyone?
Oh, me!
Back in the day, in a van
I almost drifted
That
I'm 10 years accident free.
Driving is my job.
What is it?
If I don’t go, who will move the equipment?
Because I'm moving it
They say this is an area where elk appear.
-Are you not worried?
- Because he's strong.
uh?
Just ride it
again
start the engine
I'll say it
once again
No, shift to second gear...
Come out, I'll do it
one more time
the sun is falling
Will it interfere with filming?
Let's see how good you are
From what I can guess about your condition
Take your pick
1, sulked
2, sulked
- What?
- There are up to 4 times.
3, it's not worth it
- 4...
- Okay, that's enough.
Just do it twice
Don't make meaningless examples
You're sulking
Oh no, really
I'm talking about writer Jin Moo-young.
Are you not going to write at all?
I heard you had fun writing it.
Have fun?
The first edition was published and is now out of print.
Hey, you
To those who enjoyed reading it
Why are you criticizing me like that again?
You're upset as expected
Oh no, really
‘I sulked’
yes
See you tomorrow
Good job
Yes, I will pass it on, yes.
Oh, yes, I understand, yes.
- Taerin
- Huh?
Editing scene is out
Again?
Ha, how many?
three
Ah, because you memorize the script well.
Trust and fix God
I guess you keep paying a lot.
Now, tonight
You'll have a party afterward with pork belly!
Umm
Can't I eat it?
It's a gruesome setting because I worked hard on it.
You can't get shiny after eating meat.
Memorize the script, whatever.
thank you
yes
Why?
Say ‘Ah’
No way
'Ah'
'Ah', uh
No way
I am loyal to Taerin.
Let me do something petty
Going
delicious
prone
What happens if the flower shop catches fire?
flame
The gag code is weird
Well, the sea is nice
Uh, uh...
Evil!
Are there elk?
In the sea?
Hey there
Are you okay?
Seong Je-yeon
don't come
Pretend not to know, go away
I didn't see you fall
wake up
Do you like the sea?
well
Born on the beach, that's it
Were you born on the beach?
Is that really that surprising?
no
Because I didn't know
What about you?
Do you still like the sea?
Um...
Anything is fine
Whether it’s a mountain, the sea, or a field
ok, here
Right?
The city doesn't feel like this
So
Huh? Where did you go with this one?
You had two of these, bracelets.
Huh?
That's right
When did this break?
I think you're going to be rich, really.
I remember
Remember, then
I knew it was you when I saw this
Ah...
It won't break
It lasted a long time
Seong Je-yeon
Are you still awkward with me?
throughout the filming
I have to stick with it.
I feel guilty if I forget
I feel like I dragged you into something for no reason.
Ha...
Throw it away from now on
It seems like an unnecessary word
Don't fall again while walking.
Just sleep well, you
Uh, uh, uhhh!
- hey!
- Ah, ah, ah...
Do you really want to die?
sleep well
What are you laughing at?
- What is it, a snake!
- uh?
Hey, hey, Taerin, listen...
Where are you up, huh? It's a snake
I have nowhere to go
Oh, go to the car at least, huh?
Hey
- Do you want to eat too?
- Uh
- Wake up.
- Thank you
But they said a snake would come out and it really did come out.
Where is the snake? snake?
Oh, don't come
Don't come, don't come!
- Here...
- Oh, really?
No, why do I feel like I’m making a fuss?
It's okay if you just stay still
I did that yesterday when I was working in the field.
Looks like you didn't hear me
It's dangerous
You're an actor, you have to be careful
Snake? where? where!
Where's the camera? camera!
- Let's go quickly!
- This way, here, here
Ask, be careful.
Snake, snake, snake!
You've become a monster, that senior really.
- You got bitten?
- Yes
They say there is only a public health center here.
Take the fastest boat
I think we should go out together.
Yeah, uh
I'll take care of things like receipts.
Have a nice trip
This is really for the team leader.
I'm not asking for you
- thank you
- Oh no, no.
What are you guys?
Who do you get permission from?
Do you film like this?
hello, teacher
Was it very noisy?
No, why on my land
Are you stretching out your camera like this?
Anyway, these guys from this broadcasting station are obvious, well.
No, I plant trees.
Yes, it was ok with that.
I never asked you to film
Yes, ah...
Then, let us talk for a moment.
Could you please listen...
No, well I
I haven't heard anything about it
We're almost done...
- Author, go together, stick together, stick together.
- Can I go?
- Go quickly and beg, beg, beg.
-Why, what are you talking about?
Baby, why are you like this?
What are you saying?
Teacher, you are too strong.
It's okay to plant it
They say filming is never allowed.
What, then should we just go?
Let’s abandon planting our trees
Let's pack our bags
If you miss the boat, your schedule will be messed up, so withdraw!
Let's get moving!
If you're going to throw it away
Can I stay and plant it?
If you plant this well,
These kids will grow up well.
Alone?
Hey, what we decided to plant together
How can I... alone...
And from today, I don't have any accommodation.
You can sleep anywhere, okay?
don't worry too much
Then go up quickly.
Thank you for your hard work
- Thank you for your hard work, yes.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- I'm going
- Have a hard time
Okay, well, I'm having a hard time.
Cheolsu, let’s move!
Yes, thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Senior, let’s go together quickly.
I'll finish it
I'll trust you, thank you
Oh, it's a waste.
Yes, I took all the receipts.
I'm going to go out on a boat now, yes.
Okay, see you next time, okay.
hello
Please give me a ticket for 4 o'clock.
Oh my, all the afternoon boats were canceled.
The boat can't sail because of the bad weather.
no
Is it this clear?
Right now it is
Anyway, if the boat opens tomorrow, get on it.
Ha...
Oh, it's me, that...
Can I help you?
Aren’t you having a hard time alone?
Hey, hey, give it, give it, give it, I'll do it
Save up your stamina
Because I have to plant it early tomorrow.
Ah...
Is it because it’s an island?
It rains often a day
That's right
I don't know the weather, really.
Oh, that's right, blood draw.
Blood drawn?
Do you do a health check?
Doing it periodically
It was tomorrow morning, but I couldn’t go.
Uh, give it to me
I guess we're getting older too
It's getting old.
honestly
I was wondering when I was going to plant all of this by myself.
I think it went well
If this is also one room,
I'll go to that dorm earlier and sleep.
Yeah
There's only one room left.
While we need a room
no
Two, two please
It's true, the flight was suddenly canceled
I guess all the rooms around are full?
you sleep here
Please give me that room
Yes, hello
Ah, yes, I was earlier.
The person who went 10 minutes ago...
Ah, yes, yes
I said you looked pretty earlier.
That Seoul bachelor, yes
Oh, yes, that's right, I
I said earlier that there was one room left, yes.
Ah...
yes, i understand
thank you
I had a hard time today, I was late
You too, go and rest quickly.
No, right?
the room
It's not gone, right?
Do you want to sleep in the car?
Rock, paper, scissors to be fair?
- One fight?
- Yes
Rock, paper, scissors!
Three rounds, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors!
I guess I should sleep in the car
It bothers me a bit, though.
you
You can sleep in the car
Why me?
Thank you for your hard work
Please take good care of me tomorrow as well
You are very business-like.
While sharing the same room
Ah
I have this habit
Have you ever
Have you read all my books?
I wonder if it was fun
yes
Ever since you said it yesterday
You wrote something quite hopeful.
Do you think you wanted to live like that?
Was it fun?
Ah...
I really don't want to say it because it feels like a compliment.
It was funny
some sense of kinship
I feel the same and feel the same
Well, I think it was like that in my 20s too.
How was it?
Even if I take a leave of absence from school
All my relatives rushed to me
Getting angry, soothing, scolding
They say he came to puberty late
Than when the house collapsed
I think unity was better
When you were a senior in high school
Saving time while sleeping
You studied
Well, eventually I quit.
I'm on an adventure
I kind of like it
This place is so strange
It was filmed on a low budget while rolling around like a dog.
Sometimes it goes well
What I spent money on ends up failing
I don't know the real result
But why do we continue?
Should I just get rid of it and go on an adventure?
Because there are people left?
The time we spent together, that kind of thing?
This is my first time in a scene like this
who listens to me
Am I okay?
Asking
Should we just sleep together?
Are you going to just hold hands and sleep?
yes
What? no
no
The bed
It's still one
I
Should I sleep in bed?
If I speak carefully, is that all?
fairly
Do you want to sleep together?
huh?
Be careful about this
You have to say it
Oh, I'm so tired and sleepy
Let's turn off the lights
Oh, that's right
It's not here
There is
I'm even breathing
Aren’t you too conscious of it?
Yes, there is
I feel strange
Hey, you have strange thoughts.
Isn't that what you're doing?
I didn't do it
Why don't you do it?
Are you saying do it or don't do it?
Hey, that's enough
Okay, don't do it.
you then
Quite
Because it sparkled
Why, you...
sleep well
It's past tense
I guess not now
Huh?
uh!
There isn't any?
Oh, I guess it's a dream
Ah, thank goodness
Hey, there is
Do you want to get rid of it?
I'm glad
It was a dream
Oh, hey, you really
This is why you run a flower shop.
No, it smells like dirt too.
I don't even think about anything
The sound, really, really
I only heard about the app
It's even better when you actually hear it
That's right
cactus
Are you alive?
No, why do you keep asking me why I killed him?
I thought you were going to kill me
Have a grudge against me
Should I kill you, really?
- Huh?
- Not a cactus.
Do you really want to die?
You just came from the mainland?
Ah...
No, in the first place
Why are you bringing your car to the island?
I didn't even prepare
Oh, the PD has car-related expenses.
They said they would do everything
You must have forgotten, just left.
Oh, why doesn't it explode?
Call for insurance first
Wait a minute
If you go on a boat ride
Can't open again due to bad weather
Again! Trapped on an island again!
There is only one room
Make sure to put in a contrived scene like this
Is there drama?
Oh, it's contrived.
Our Taerin is currently appearing in dramas as well.
The car that was in good condition suddenly broke down.
Why? Because it has to break down
What are you looking at!
what?
'gas station'?
‘When you run out of gas’?
Ah, it's done
They say there’s a gas station nearby.
I'll get the oil
Ah, hey
Hey, no
I heard that wild boars appear here earlier.
I received a safety text message
What if I run into someone while I'm alone?
Hey, that's more contrived.
Are you worried that your insurance premiums will go up?
You're not calling, right?
Ugh
This is an area excluded from business trip service.
give it
Ah, why say that now!
kid!
Oh, I really am
I'm a person who follows the milestones.
The boats cut off and the cars stopped.
What, have you always lived like that?
According to the signpost?
huh?
no
A map I've never seen before
I wonder if I've ever followed you
Um...
I'm not even sure there's a way
There were many times I had to go
Like now?
Oh, that's right
You said you liked adventure
- Wow
-Why?
I was looking forward to it from the moment I arrived on location.
What?
planting trees
When should I try it?
If you plant it well like this
Grow well and neatly
I think there might be
In order to grow to a size worth seeing...
It will take about 5 years
It will be really pretty when the flowers bloom
What is the language of flowers?
I won't tell you
Chi
- Hey, Seonwoohae.
- Huh?
you really
Why did you say you would appear?
Are you still curious about that?
The reason why you refused to invite me all this time is
It makes so much sense.
But what I accepted was
No matter how much I think about it, I still don’t understand it.
To a lost friend
heart
your heart is true
You look great
interest
The language of flowers from the trees we planted
What, when did you search?
I didn't have time to do that
You made it up, why?
Puhahahaha!
You wrote it very well.
What is it, can I reach it?
I can reach it, I can reach it, I can reach it, uh!
I reached it, I reached it!
I'm so crazy I'm dying
Calm down, I won't eat you.
If you don't like it, avoid it.
What if you don’t like it?
Thank goodness
What happens to us now?
We even kissed
You can't go back before that.
What did I do?
I think it would be more awkward if I went quietly.
You are nineteen
It stands up like a stone beak
It pops up at any time
I tripped
The original publisher went bankrupt...
The original work is out of print
The contract only says ‘original author’.
Why come back!
After that happened, mom
You didn't come!
Can I go on a date here?
With whom?
A guy you like?
I'm curious about what you're doing
This is the beginning of interest.
If the guy who kicked me hangs on
Isn’t it rather good?
If I don't meet anyone
Would you like to meet me?